{
    "subject": "resource/Hawking_(2013_film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "Nathan Chapple",
    "human_readable": "The film Hawking (2013 film) stars Nathan Chapple.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9129206538200378,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Hawking (2013)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9022517204284668,
            "question": "What role did Nathan Chapple play in the film Hawking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7970548272132874,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that stars Nathan Chapple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116621732711792,
            "question": "Is Nathan Chapple known for other roles besides his role in Hawking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6251236200332642,
            "question": "Who was the subject of the film Hawking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5740101337432861,
            "question": "In what year was the film Hawking released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5317586660385132,
            "question": "Is the film Hawking a biographical drama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5310972929000854,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film Hawking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38488996028900146,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in the film Hawking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30787360668182373,
            "question": "Did the film Hawking receive any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Hawking (2013 film) stars Nathan Chapple.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3540_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in the film Hawking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3540_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of the film Hawking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3540_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the film Hawking a biographical drama?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3540_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3540_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to test more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. Specifically, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3540/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt states that \"Hawking is a biopic about Stephen Hawking the celebrity physicist who has become an emblem of science, a medical miracle, and a hero to everyone struggling with a disability.  Hawking was well-received in its world premiere at Austin's SXSW Film Festival.\" It also mentions that Nathan Chapple is featured as Stephen Hawking in the biographical documentary \"Hawking\" (2013)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the 2013 documentary \"Hawking\" featured Nathan Chapple as an actor, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}